A Guide to the Rosanna Bencoach papers, 1932-2014
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Rosanna Bencoach papers, 1932-2014
The Library of Virginia
43964
4.875 cu. ft. and 12 boxes
Rosanna Bencoach
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Rosanna Bencoach, Richmond, Virginia.
Scope and Content
Papers, 1932-2014, of Rosanna Bencoach of Richmond, Virginia, containing ads, books, booklets, brochures, bumper stickers, cassette tapes, envelopes, fliers, letters, magazines, postcards, programs, reports, rosters, stamps, stereographic cards, VHS tapes, DVDs, and other papers mainly concerning Virginia politics from the 1970s through the 2010s, including state and national campaigns, the Virginia Republican Party, the Virginia legislature, and various political organizations. Collection also includes materials on the Reynolds Metals Company, Native Americans, national parks, University of Virginia basketball, the Washington Redskins, the Waltons television show, postcards, and audio and video recordings regarding politics and history.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
Series I: Political papers, 1960-2014.
Series II: General papers, 1932-ca. 2007.
Contents List
- Series I: Political papers, 1960-2014., Extent: 9 boxes (3.825 cubic feet). (Box 1-9)
  Political papers, 1960-2014, contain ads, articles, brochures, fliers, newsletters, photographs, reports, and other papers, as well as audio and video recordings concerning elections for president, governor, Congress, General Assembly, and other offices. Papers include materials for the Virginia Republican party and for institutes connected with the University of Virginia. Papers also contain records regarding political activites of elected officials.
  - George Allen--House of Delegates elections, 26th district and 58th district, 1979, 1982, 1983. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - George Allen--Congress (7th district), 1991-1992. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - George Allen--campaign for governor, 1993, Republican Party nomination. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - George Allen--campaign for governor, 1993, articles, etc. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - George Allen--campaign for governor, 1993, campaign news releases. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - George Allen--campaign for governor, 1993, brochures, programs, sample ballot, business card. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - George Allen--campaign for governor, 1993, public correspondence. (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - George Allen--campaign for governor, 1993, general papers. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - George Allen--campaign for governor, 1993, Friends of George Allen. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - George Allen--campaign for governor, 1993, Virginians for George Allen. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - George Allen--campaign for governor, 1993, Opportunity 2001: George Allen's Blueprint for Creating Jobs in Virginia. (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - George Allen--campaign for governor, 1993, The George Allen Plan for Controlling Tuition Costs. (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - George Allen--campaign for governor, 1993, The George Allen Plan for Workfare: Saving Taxpayers' Dollars by Transforming Welfare Dependency into Employment. (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - George Allen--campaign for governor, 1993, The Champion Schools Initiative: George Allen's Plan to Improve Public Schools by Setting High Academic Standards and Encouraging Local Innovation. (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - George Allen--campaign for governor, 1993, Revitalizing Virginia's Inner-Cities: George Allen's Plan for Restoring Hope Through Expanded Opportunity. (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - George Allen--campaign for governor, 1993, Violent Crime in Virginia: The George Allen Plan for Abolishing Parole. (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - George Allen--campaign for governor, 1993, bumper stickers. (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - George Allen--Governor, 1992-1997, Juvenile Justice. (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - George Allen--Governor, 1994-1995, Lightning Does the Work: Governor Allen's First 500 Days.. (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - George Allen--Governor, 1994, Vision for Virginia: 1994 Agency Leadership Workshop. (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - George Allen--Governor, 25 May 1995, Public safety accomplishments, current tasks, and future objectives. (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - George Allen--Governor, 15 October 1996, Second Annual Governor's Forum on Crime. (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - George Allen--Governor, 26 September 1997, remarks of the honorable Jay Timmons, Chief of Staff at the Virginia Correctional Association 1997 Annual Conference. (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - George Allen--Governor, 14 January 1998, State of the Commonwealth address. (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - George Allen--Governor, 1994-1997, undated, general papers. (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - George Allen--Governor, selected speeches. (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - George Allen--campaign for U.S. Senate, 2000, papers. (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - George Allen--U.S. Senate, ca. 2001-2007, papers. (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - George Allen--campaign for U.S. Senate, 2006, papers. (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - George Allen--campaign for U.S. Senate, ca. 2000, 2006, bumper stickers. (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - George Allen--campaign for U.S. Senate, 2012, papers. (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Susan Allen,interview with Style Weekly21 January 1997. (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Howard Baker--campaign for President, 1980, U.S. Republican Party nomination. (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Howard Baker, address at the 1984 Republican National Convention, 20 August 1984. (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Gerald Baliles--campaign for governor, 1985, anti-Baliles ad. (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Steve Baril--campaign for attorney general, Virginia Republican Party primary, 2005, papers. (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Viola Baskerville--campaign for lieutenant governor, Virginia Democratic Party primary, 2005, papers. (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Rob Bell--House of Delegates (58th district), 2012-2014, Christmas cards. (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Rob Bell--campaign for attorney general, Virginia Republican Party nomination, 2013, papers. (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Joseph Benedetti--campaign for attorney general, 1989, bumper sticker. (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Don Beyer--campaign for lieutenant governor, 1989, flier. (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Don Beyer--campaign for governor, 1997, papers. (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Don Beyer--campaign for Congress (8th district), 2014, bumper sticker. (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Bill Bolling--campaign for lieutenant governor, 2005, brochures, etc. (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Bill Bolling--Lieutenant Governor, ca. 2006-2010, 100 Ideas for the Future of Virginia. (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Bill Bolling--campaign for governor, Virginia Republican Party nomination, 2013, ad. (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Rick Boucher--campaign for Congress (9th district), ca. 1982, bumper sticker. (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - George H. W. Bush--campaign for president, 1988, papers. (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - George H. W. Bush--campaign for president, 1988, papers. (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - George H. W. Bush--President, 1989, undated, program, photographs. (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - George H. W. Bush--President, 1992 presidential calendar. (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - George H. W. Bush--campaign for president, 1992, papers. (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - George H. W. Bush--campaign for president, 1992, Agenda for American Renewal. (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - George W. Bush--campaign for president, 2000, America 2000: An Education Strategy. (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - George W. Bush--campaign for president, 2000, papers. (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - George W. Bush--campaign for president, 2004, papers. (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Harry F. Byrd, Jr.--U.S. Senate, ca. 1981-1983, gallary pass for 97th Congress. (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Leslie Byrne--campaign for lieutenant governor, Virignia Democratic primary, 2005, flier. (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Eric Cantor--campaign for Congress (7th district), ca. 2000-2008, brochure, bumper stickers. (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Eric Cantor--campaign for Congress (7th district), 2012, papers. (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Eric Cantor--campaign for Congress (7th district), ca. 2012-2014, bumper stickers and flier. (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Eric Cantor--Congress (7th district), 2013, birthday celebration invitation. (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Eric Cantor--campaign for Congress (7th district), Virginia Republican primary, 2014, papers. (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Jimmy Carter--campaign for president, 1976, brochure. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Jimmy Carter--campaign for president, 1980, papers. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Jimmy Carter--campaign for president, 1980, anti-Carter ad. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - John Chichester--campaign for lieutenant governor, 1985, papers. (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Wes Clark--campaign for president, Democratic Party primary, 2004, brochure. (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Bill Clinton/Al Gore--campaign for president/vice president, 1992, bumper sticker. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Marshall Coleman--campaign for governor, 1981, papers. (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Marshall Coleman/Nathan Miller/Wyatt Durrette--campaign for governor/lieutenant governor/attorney general, 1981, 81 Home Victory Program! (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Marshall Coleman/Nathan Miller/Wyatt Durrette--campaign for governor/lieutenant governor/attorney genral, 1981, 81 Phone Victory Program! (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Marshall Coleman--campaign for governor, Virginia Republican party nomination, 1989, papers. (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Marshall Coleman--campaign for governor, 1989, Coleman for Governor: 1989 Campaign Victory Manual (red). (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Marshall Coleman--campaign for governor, 1989, Coleman for Governor: 1989 Campaign Victory Manual (blue). (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Marshall Coleman--campaign for governor, 1989, Making 20 Years Mean 20 Years: The Marshall Coleman Plan to Keep Violent Criminals Behind Bars and Off Our Streets. (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Marshall Coleman--campaign for governor, 1989, manuals, forms. (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Marshall Coleman--campaign for governor, 1989, Robert Goodman Agency: State of Virginia past voting analysis. (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Marshall Coleman--campaign for governor, 1989, Veterans for Coleman. (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Marshall Coleman--campaign for governor, 1989, abortion. (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Marshall Coleman--campaign for governor, 1989, Wilder disinformation reports. (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Marshall Coleman--campaign for governor, 1989, memorandums to campaign staff. (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Marshall Coleman--campaign for governor, 1989, press releases. (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Marshall Coleman--campaign for governor, 1989, brochures, fliers, ads. (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Marshall Coleman--campaign for governor, 1989, bumper stickers. (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Marshall Coleman--campaign for governor, 1989, general papers. (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Marshall Coleman--campaign for governor, 1989, photographs. (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Marshall Coleman--campaign for governor, 1989, election day, 7 November 1989. (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Marshall Coleman--campaign for governor, 1989, post-election analysis. (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Sean Connaughton--campaign for lieutenant governor, Virginia Republican Party primary, 2005, papers. (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Gerry Connolly--campaign for Congress (11th district), 2012, bumper stickers and flier. (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Philip M. Crane--campaign for president, National Republican nomination, 1980, papers. (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Ken Cuccinelli--campaign for governor, 2013, bumper stickers and fliers. (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Eddy Dalton--campaign for Virginia Senate (12th district), 1987, papers (reference to Jim Gilmore--Henrico County Commonwealth's attorney race). (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Eddy Dalton--campaign for lieutenant governor, 1989, program. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Jeannemarie Davis--campaign for lieutenant governor, Virginia Republican Pary nomination, 2013, papers. (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - John Dalton--campaign for governor, 1977, papers. (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - John Dalton--governor, 6 June 1981, remarks, state Republican Party convention. (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - John Dalton, funeral bulletin, 1 August 1986. (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Dick Davis--campaign for lieutenant governor, 1981, flier. (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Jo Ann Davis--campaign for Congress (1st district), ca. 2004-2006, flier. (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Bob Dole--campaign for president, 1996, flier. (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Michael Dukakis--campaign for president, 1988, anti-Dukakis pamphlet. (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Wyatt Durrette--campaign for attorney general, 1981, papers. (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Wyatt Durrette, speech at National Convention, Young Americans for Freedom, 23 August 1984. (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Wyatt Durrette--campaign for governor, 1985, leadership manual and mass meeting planning. (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Wyatt Durrette--campaign for governor, 1985, The Educational Challenge Before Us. (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Wyatt Durrette--campaign for governor, 1985, articles. (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Wyatt Durrette--campaign for governor, 1985, brochures, fliers, stickers, etc. (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Wyatt Durrette--campaign for governor, 1985, papers. (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Wyatt Durrette/John Chichester/Buster O'Brien--campaign for governor/lieutenant governor/attorney general, 1985, papers. (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Mark Early--campaign for attorney general, 1997, papers. (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Mark Early--campaign for governor, Virginia Republican Party nomination, 2001, convention guide. (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Mark Early--campaign for governor, 2001,. (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Mark Early/Jay Katzen/Jerry Kilgore--campaign for governor/lieutenant governor/attorney general, 2001, flier. (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Ed Eck--campaign for House of Delegates (68th district), 1991, mailing. (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Guy Farley--campaign for lieutenant governor, Virginia Republican Party nomination, 1981, papers. (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - George Fitch--campaign for governor, Virginia Republican Party primary, 2005, flier. (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Randy Forbes--campaign for Congress (4th district), ca. 2002-2008, bumper sticker and flier. (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Gerald Ford--campaign for president, 1976, papers. (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Joh Foust--campaign for Congress (10th district), 2014, flier. (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - John T. Frey--campaign for attorney general, Virginia Republican Party nomination, 2013, flier. (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Ed Gillespie--campaign for U.S. Senate, 2014, bumper stickers. (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Jim Gilmore--campaign for attorney general, 1993, papers. (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Jim Gilmore--campaign for governor, 1997, papers. (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Jim Gilmore--campaign for governor, 1997, bumper stickers. (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Jim Gilmore--Governor, 1997-1998, transition and inauguration. (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Jim Gilmore--Governor, 1998-2002,. (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Jim Gilmore--campaign for president, 2008, letter. (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Jim Gilmore--campaign for U.S.Senate, 2008, papers. (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Newt Gingrich--American Opportunity pamphlet. (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Mills Godwin--campaign for governor, 1973, flier. (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Virgil Goode--campaign for Congress (5th district), ca. 1996-2008, bumper sticker. (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Rudy Guliani--campaign for president, National Republican Party primary, 2008, papers. (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - John Hager--campaign for lieutenant governor, 1997, papers. (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - John Hager--campaign for governor, Virginia Republican Party nomination, 2001, brochures, video. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - J. E. Chip Harding--campaign for sheriff (Albemarle County), 2007, fliers. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Paul Harris--campaign for House of Delegates (58th district), ca. 1997-1999, bumper sticker. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Charles Haugh--campaign for Virginia Senate (25th district), 1980, flier. (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Mike Herring--campaign for Commonwealth's attorney (Richmond), 2005, fliers. (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Oliver White Hill, memorial program, 11 August 2007. (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Elsie Goodwyn Holland--campaign for Congress (3rd district), 1996, flier. (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Linwood Holton--campaign for governor, 1969, photograph. (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Linwood Holton--campaign for U.S. Senate, Virginia Republican Party nomination, 1978, poster. (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Henry Howell--campaign for governor, 1977, article, The Times of Charlottesville. (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Henry Howell, University of Virginia class, 1981. (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - E. W. Jackson--campaign for lieutenant governor, 2013, fliers. (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Tim Kaine--campaign for governor, 2005, anti-Kaine bumper sticker. (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Tim Kaine--Governor, ca. 2006-2010, photograph. (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Tim Kaine--campaign for U.S. Senate, 2012, anti-Kaine ads. (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Jay Katzen--campaign for lieutenant governor, 2001, brochure. (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Jack Kemp, papers, 1983-1984. (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Jack Kemp--campaign for president, national Republican Party nomination, 1988, papers. (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Jack Kennedy--campaign for Virginia Senate (40th district), 1991, voter's guide. (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Alan Keyes--campaign for president, national Republican Party nomination, 2000, brochure. (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Jerry Kilgore--campaign for attorney general, 2001, papers. (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Jerry Kilgore--campaign for governor, 2005, papers. (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Jerry Kilgore/Bill Bolling/Bob McDonnell--campaign for governor/lieutenant governor/attorney general, 2005, mailing and bumper sticker. (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Melvin Law--campaign for House of Delegates (71st district), Virginia Democratic Party primary, 2005, fliers. (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Scott Lingamfelter--campaign for lieutenant governor, Virginia Republican Party nomination, 2013, papers. (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Steve Martin--campaign for lieutenant governor, Virginia Republican Party nomination, 2013, fliers. (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - John McCain--campaign for president, 2008, bumper stickers and card. (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Jennifer McClellan--campaign for House of Delegates (71st district), 2005, papers. (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Bob McDonnell--campaign for attorney general, 2005, papers. (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Bob McDonnell--Attorney General, 24 May 2007, Honoring Our Heroes program. (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Bob McDonnell--campaign for governor, 2009, papers. (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Bob McDonnell--Governor, ca. 2011, Opportunity for Virginia PAC. (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Andy Miller--campaign for U.S. Senate, 1978, newspaper. (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Harris Miller--campaign for U.S. Senate, Virginia Democratic primary, 2006, papers. (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Jim Miller--campgin for U.S. Senate, Virginia Republican Party nomination, 1994, booklet. (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Nathan Miller--campaign for lieutenant governor, 1981, bumper stickers. (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Walter Mondale--campaign for president, 1984, anti-Mondale ad. (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Richard Nixon--Presidential Library, 19 July 1990. (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Tommy Norment--campaign for Virginia Senate (3rd district), Virginia Republican primary, 2011, flier. (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Oliver North--campaign for U.S. Senate, 1994, papers. (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Barack Obama--campaign for president, 2012, anti-Obama ads. (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Helen Obenshain--Republican National Committeewoman, ca. 1980s, flier. (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Mark Obenshain--campaign for attorney general, 2013, papers. (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Richard Obenshain, articles, 1972, 1983. (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Stan Parris--campaign for governor, Virginia Republican primary, 1989, flier. (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Ron Paul--campaign for president, National Republican Party nomination, 2012, brochure. (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Chris Peace--campaign for House of Delegates (97th district), ca. 2011-2013, bumper stickers. (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - A. L. Philpott article, 1985. (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Wayne Powell--campaign for Congress (7th district), 2012, anti-Powell ads. (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Jamie Radtke--campaign for U.S. Senate, 2012, flier. (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Ronald Reagan--campaign for president, 1980, papers. (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Ronald Reagan--campaign for president, 1984,. (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Ronald Reagan--President, 1981-1989, papers. (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Christening of the U.S.S. Ronald Reagan, 4 March 2001. (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Jack Reid--campaign for House of Delegates (72nd district), ca. 1995-1997, flier. (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Chuck Robb--campaign for governor, 1981, papers. (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Chuck Robb--campaign for U.S. Senate, 1988, anti-Robb ads. (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Chuck Robb--U.S. Senate, October 1991, Tai Collins Playboy interview. (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Pat Robertson--campaign for president, National Republican primary, 1987, His Proposals Step by Step. (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - J. Kenneth Robinson--campaign for Congress (7th district), 1978-1983, papers. (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Mitt Romney--campaign for president, 2012, flier, bumper sticker. (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Mitt Romney--campaign for president, 2012, anti-Romney ads on birth control. (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Mitt Romney/Paul Ryan--campaign for president/vice president, 2012, sign. (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - David Sisk--campaign for House of Delegates (97th district), ads,. (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Pete Snyder--campaign for lieutenant governor, Virginia Republican Party nomination, 2013, papers. (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Pete Snyder--campaign for lieutenant governor, Virginia Republican Party nomination, 2013, anti-Snyder ad. (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Corey Stewart--campaign for lieutenant governor, Virginia Republican Party nomination, 2013, papers. (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Corey Stewart--campaign for lieutenant governor, Virginia Republican Party nomination, 2013, anti-Stewart ads. (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Susan Stimpson--campaign for lieutenant governor, Virginia Republican Party nomination, 2013, ads. (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Mary Sue Terry--campaign for governor, 1993, brochure. (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Mary Sue Terry/Don Beyer/Bill Dolan--campaign for governor/lieutenant governor/attorney general, 1993, ad. (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Fred Thompson--campaign for president, National Republican Party nomination2008, flier. (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - John Thompson--campaign for Richmond city council (2nd district), 1990, papers. (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Paul Trible--campaign for U.S. Senate, 1982, papers. (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Paul Trible--campaign for governor, Virginia Republican primary, 1989, brochure. (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - William Wampler--campaign for Virginia Senate (40th district), 1991, papers. (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Elizabeth Taylor Warner article, June 1980, Richmond Lifestyle. (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - John Warner--campaign for U.S. Senate, 1978, papers. (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - John Warner--campaign for U.S. Senate, 1984, brochure and bumper sticker. (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - John Warner--campaign for U.S. Senate, 1990, newsletter. (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - John Warner--campaign for U.S. Senate, undated, bumper sticker. (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - John Warner--U.S. Senate, 1979-2001, papers. (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Mark Warner--campaign for governor, 2001, brochure. (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Mark Warner--Governor, 2002, ticket and photograph. (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Mark Warner--Governor, 12 January 2005, Commonwealth prayer breakfast. (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Mark Warner--campaign for U.S. Senate, 2014, papers. (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Mark Warner/Don Beyer--campaign for U.S. Senate/Congress (8th district), 2014, flier. (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Mark Warner/Don Beyer/John Foust/Gerald Connolly--campaign for U.S. Senate/Congress (8th district, 10th district, 11th district), 2014, sample ballot. (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Michelle Welch--campaign for Commonwealth's attorney (Richmond), 2005, papers. (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Doug Wilder--campaign for governor, 1989, papers. (Box 6, Folder 39)